Hello hello everyone welcome to my YouTube
channel our topic today is
about super top up loan of ICICI Lombard General Insurance whose name is
Health Booster. ICICI Lombard is
a very big brand in General Insurance company
so today we will describe all the plans in details
so let's
talk about the features the most unique
feature is the preview benefit reset
benefit means whatever sum insured
you have selected, 10 lakh, 20 lakh
as soon as it is used, the company
resets the same sum insured the next day the condition
is that the same person will
not get the benefit of this resort benefit for the same disease
for example if a person has
used his preview sum insured for cancer then again when reset benefit happens he
cannot use that same benefit for cancer he can use it for any other disease let's
talk about second future see what is the
meaning of Loota Day Care  This is the
treatment for which you do not need to be admitted in the hospital for 24
hours.
Now you go and get your treatment done and
come back home, then
ICICI Lombard covers 150 days in this plan. The
third feature is Ayush treatment,
Ayurvedic, Unani and Homeopathic, whatever
your treatment is, up-to-date treatment is
covered in this product. The condition is
that yours should be a government hospital
or a government approved center. Let's
talk about the next feature, domiciliary
treatment. This means the treatment
which for some reason you have to get done from home, then the
company will cover it on time.
Next is donor expenses,
if for any reason the policy holder needs an
organ, then whoever
donates his organ is also covered
up-to-the-minute by the company.
Free hospitalization is for seven days, post
hospitalization is for three days. Ambulance
cover is your top 250. If we talk about the policy period, it is
one year, two years and three years.
If you take a plan for 2 years, then the
company will cover it for ten days.  If
you take a plan for three years, the
company gives a discount of 12.5 percent.
Talking about a range, you can select any policy between Rs 5 lakh to Rs 50 lakh. There is
life long renewal. In this policy, the
deductible is Rs 34 lakh and the maximum is Rs 5 lakh.
Deductible means the amount you
select that after this amount
I have to use the super top up line, that is
called your deductible amount.
Talking about the planner option, the maximum
amount teachers and students
can share in the policy is free. Existing
disease: If you have any disease before taking the policy, the
company covers it after two years.
This is a unique feature because
most companies give you coverage after three or four years.
You get a separate tax benefit
under section 8d. Now, if you are
taking Rs 225 for your parents who are above sixty years of age,
then you
can avail tax benefits up to Rs 50,000. Its rules  The
regulations will be like a normal policy,
which has a waiting period,
your waiting period is one month, two years
waiting period or those with permanent exclusion,
so this was all the information
about ICICI Lombard's Super Top Up Loan, sir, we will keep bringing such information,
so please like our channel and
subscribe, thank you for
watching.